Speaker: What is a bucket list?
It’s a list of things that you want to do before you die.
The expression comes from an English idiom, “to kick the bucket,” which means to die.
Some people make a new bucket list every year.
Others start one when they’re young and keep on adding to it.
Others set a time limit, for example, “Things I want to do before I’m 30.”
What kind of things do people put on them?
All sorts of things.
Many are to do with travel, for example, travel to all seven continents,
go on a cruise
see the northern lights
go on a safari.
Others are about adventures, for example,
do a bungee jump
hike through a rainforest
ride a horse on the beach.
Some involve learning new skills, for example,
learn to scuba dive
learn to play an instrument
learn to play chess
learn to cook
And others are just random things people would like to do, for example,
see the sun rise
go on a blind date
be an extra in a movie
get a tattoo
be on TV
see a tennis match at Wimbledon
read a classic novel
What would you put on your bucket list?